A Finding Aid to the Tomás Ybarra-Frausto Research Material on Chicano Art, 1965-2004, in the Archives of American Art AAA.ybartoma
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, 1965-1997; Series 1
  - Oversize Poster from Movimiento Artistico del Rio Salado (MARS), 1982 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletters from Murals, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Posters from Lomas Garza, Carmen folders, 1988, 1990 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Mexican Museum, San Francisco, 1991 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Galería Otra Vez, Los Angeles, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Garcia, Rupert, 1978 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Catalog from Mexican Fine Arts Center Museum, 1987 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Artists' Books, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Arte Chicano Chronology, 1982 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Chicanarte, 1975 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Posters & Illustrated Poem from League of United Chicano Artists (LUCHA), 1979, 1981, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Guerrero, El Zarco, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Herrera, Juan Felipe, undated (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Posters from Galería de la Raza/Studio 24, 1992, 1994 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletter and Catalog from Dí de los Muertos, 1990-1991 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Posters from INTAR Latin American Gallery, 1983-1986, 1991, 1996 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletter Issues from Hispanic Cultures Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Magazine from Chicano Photographers, 1993 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Magazine from Chismearte, 1981 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Calendars from Buitrón, Robert, 1990-1991 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Corazón de Aztlán, 1981 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Magazines from Cholos - Low Rider, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Posters from Hecho En Califas, 2000-2001 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Border Arts Workshop, 1987 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Salvo, Dana, 1987 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletters from Galería Posada, 2004, 2005 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Magazines from Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center Tontantzin, 1984-2004 (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Fuegos en Aztlín, 1980 (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletters from Revista Rio Bravo (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from Parilla, Eliezer (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletters from Mission District - La Razon Mestiza II (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Magazines from Colorado - La Voz (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Newsletters from La Comunidad (Box 31 (sol))
  - Oversize Prints from Meta Studio I, circa 1981 (Box 30 (sol))
  - Oversize Poster from CALIFAS, 1981 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from INTAR, 1987 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Galería de la Raza/Studio 24, 1982 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Festival Internacional de la Raza, 1985 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Arizona, 1978 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Posters from Photography, 1990-1992 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Texas - Arte Chicano, circa 1979 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Posters from Lomas Garza, Carmen, 1985, circa 1989, undated (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Romero, Frank, 1984 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Montoya, Malaquias, 1987 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Arte Picante: Contemporary Chicano Art, circa 1975 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Vasquez, Emigdio, 1981 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from University of California at Los Angeles, 1984 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Mission Cultural Center, 1981 (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Poster from Chicanarte, circa 1976 (Box OV 32)